This is the story of my idol Ram,
Ini adalah cerita idolaku Ram,
a human revered as God.
manusia yang dipuja sebagai Tuhan.
Whose life was a celebration of righteousness.
Yang hidupnya adalah tentang kebenaran.
His name was Raghav.
Namanya Raghav.
Whose righteousness shattered the arrogance of evil.
Yang kebenarannya dapat menghancurkan kejahatan setan.
This is the saga of Raghunandan
Ini adalah kisah Raghunandan
An epic that has existed through the ages
Sebuah legenda yang telah ada selama berabad-abad
This is the story of Ramayan.
Ini adalah kisah Ramayana.
Grant me some alms.
Percaya padaku.
You are the prince of Ayodhya.
Kamu adalah puteri Ayodhya.
Just say the word and the entire army will fight with you.
Katakan satu kalimat saja dan pasukan akan siap bertempur bersamamu.
That would be against my righteousness.
Itu akan bertentangan dengan kebenaran saya.
So is your righteousness more valuable to you than sister-in-law's life?
Begitu juga kebaikan lebih berharga bagimu daripada kehidupan kakak iparmu?
Janaki is my life.
Janaki adalah hidupku.
But my righteousness is more precious than my life.
Tapi kebaikan lebih berharga daripada hidupku.
It doesn't suit you to sit at my feet.
Tidak pantas bagimu untuk duduk di kakiku.
Our deeds define our character, not our birth.
Perbuatan kita menentukan karakter kita, bukan kelahiran kita.
Realize your own powers, Bajrang.
Sadarilah kekuatanmu sendiri, Bajrang.
Only you alone can do it.
Hanya kamu sendiri yang bisa melakukan itu.
Hail Shri Ram!
Salam Shri Ram!
Raghav had broken the Shivdhanush to marry me.
Raghav telah melanggar Shivdhanush untuk menikahiku.
Now he must break Raavan's arrogance.
Sekarang dia harus menghancurkan kesombongan Raavan.
Do not fight for me!
Jangan berperang untuku!
Fight for that glory,
Berperanglah untuk kemuliaan,
where people will bow down with respect when they hear your name.
dimana orang akan menghormatimu ketika mendengar namamu.
Will you fight?
Kamu akan berperang?
Then march on and pierce the enemy's hearts with the victory flag!
Tembuslah pertahanan musuh dan kembali dengan bendera kemenangan!
You already have everything this universe has to offer,
Kamu telah memiliki semua yang diberikan alam semesta,
but you still remain a Demon.
tapi tetap saja kamu menjadi Iblis.
Make Lakshmi your consort and you will become Narayan.
Jadikan Lakshmi sebagai pendampingmu dan kamu akan menjadi Narayan.
Hail Shri Ram!
Salam Shri Ram!